vusolutions.com 2004-06-02

# VFS Privacy Policy

| |  **

NOTICE OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY

**

**Information Only-No Response Necessary**

At **Vu Financial Solutions, Inc.** , we are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. We want you to understand what information we collect and how we use it. We treat nonpublic personal information in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

****

**Information We Collect:**

Our firm collects "nonpublic personal information" about you from the following sources:

> > • Information we receive from you on applications, documents used in preparing tax returns, or other forms;
>> 
>> • Information about your transactions with us or others; and
>> 
>> • Information we receive from third parties, such as a credit bureau.

"Nonpublic personal information" is nonpublic information about you that we obtain in connection with providing financial products or services, including accounting or tax preparation services, to you.

****

**Information We Disclose:**

We do not disclose any nonpublic personal information about you to anyone, except as permitted or required by law. We disclose your personal information only when it is necessary to provide services you requested. Some examples of disclosures to a third party are credit reporting agency, lender, closing agent, or servicing agent.

If you decide to close your account(s) or become an inactive customer, we will adhere to the privacy policies and practices as described in this notice.

****

**Our Security Procedures:**

We restrict access to your personal and account information to those employees and/or professionals who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information.

****

**Questions:**

Thank you for the opportunity to serve you. Your relationship and trusts are very important to us. If you have any questions regarding this Notice or other matters, please feel free to contact us at (617) 381-9700 or email us at [privacy@vusolutions.com](mailto:privacy@vusolutions.com)
